{
	"angel": [
	{
		"qDate": "2012-05-18",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "When i got to go to the store with Grandpa and he bought my Ariel doll."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "You're still in school, and you don't do all those adultish things like pay bills and have an account in the bank."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "Humble."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "I would tell Daddy to work at the house like mommy does."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "I'd be a black pony because I think black looks like a good color on a horse, and I also think baby ponies are cute."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "Let's see... school work... my big book... watching TV... creating Mr. Quacker."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "When I was reading quotes from the kids."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Creating Mr. Quacker.  Because Mr. Quacker is a cute ducky, and it was my first ducky."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Playing Barbies probably."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
			"answer": "Harmony and Charity: playful. Tony: awesome."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "I'm guessing it would be like helping Grandpa with the babies."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "Doing a whole whole bunch of musicals and going to college."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Go swimming!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "I would have $40/week... actually, I'd get $100/week!  And I would go to the Disney Store, and buy the dazzling, dazzling Rapunzel doll that was $100.  I'd waste all my money on that!  Actually, I would because she's beautiful."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "A kind heart."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
			"answer": "Go to Lego Land, and go to Science City."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
			"answer": "That would be Zombie Cafe (iPad game), when they serve a lump of green stuff and grossness."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
			"answer": "If I had $1000, I would first tithe, then I would spend $100 of it on a really, really expensive Barbie.  And I would spend another part of it at a garage sale, then I would donate some of it, then I would tithe again... I think.... I wouldn't donate it.... I would take the donate half, and I would give it to my mother and father!  All done."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "I want to be a designer because I like how you make clothes and fabrics and stuff."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
			"answer": "With peanuts, and I know it’s not made with butter.  They smash the peanuts, take out the acid, and put the acid in the peanut butter jar."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
			"answer": "Umm... 20 feet tall?"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
			"answer": "Oh I know I know!  10 feet tall."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
			"answer": "I know what you do at work!  You work on Rhythm City and ask people to buy the DVD."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
			"answer": "on Netflix and the internet.  I think shows get on Netflix I think it’s because... I’m just saying all the wrong words... I bet it’s because people let them use their shows on Netflix, and Netflix would pay them to let them use their shows."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
			"answer": "Because I fit in well, and I’m really good with little kids"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Why do you think the sky is blue?",
			"answer": "I think the sky is blue because it goes well with the grass.  Blue and green go good together."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2014-08-17",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could spend your time doing only one activity, what would that activity be? Why?",
			"answer": "Mmm...it would be....that's a hard one...I would go across the world singing because I think it would be fun singing for a lot of people. And I like singing."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could learn how to do something new next week, what would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "I would choose learning how to play the guitar because I've always wanted to learn and I think it would be fun to sing along while I played."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could do something to cheer up a group of kids less fortunate than you, what would you do? Why?",
			"answer": "Anything? I would get them a big dinner and give them the leftovers to take home."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could pick something in your bedroom that would last forever, what would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "My baptismal plaque because it would always remind me that I  made a commitment to Jesus and that He's my savior."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could send an e-mail or text message to anyone in the world knowing that they would in fact open it and read it, to whom would you send it? What would you say? Why?",
			"answer": "Well, I would send it to...ok, so, if they could read it, I would send it to Harmony and Charity and I would say \"Harmony and Charity, you are amazeballs sisters and I'm glad you're in my family.\" And I would put bubbles and hearts and butterflies all over it."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could have a super power, what would you choose to have? Why? What super-hero name would you choose?",
			"answer": "I would probably choose teleportation and teleport to different places in time; because if I had teleportation, I would be able to tell what happened with Adam and Eve, and ride with Noah's ark, and see all the big scary giants in the Promised Land.  And I'd go 100 years in the future to see what the technology is like; my name would be...when I play with Adam, it's always Emma....but I'd choose The Incredible Girl...unless it's already taken."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could have any animal in the world and shrink it down to a mouse-sized pet, what animal would you choose? Why? What name would you give it? Why?",
			"answer": "I would choose a tiger because if I shrunk a tiger it wouldn't hurt if it bit me.  And I'd be able to keep it in a small, enclosed space and be able to play with it.  I would name it Batman because it has black stripes."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Where do you think would be the most exciting place in the United States to live? To visit? How about in the world?",
			"answer": "Live: Beverly Hills, CA.  Or Disneyworld.  Visit: Hollywood.  World: Either Paris or Italy"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Can you think of three things we could do to make meals together more interesting and fun for everyone in the family?",
			"answer": "We could ... umm... not sure."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the silliest thing you've ever done? What would you like to do to top it? Why?",
			"answer": "I came up with the word, \"MERF!\"; To top it, I would paint my face like a clown and then go around giving everyone hugs."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite sport or game? If you could change one rule, what would you change? Why?",
			"answer": "Cheerleading; ...I can't change cheerleading rules! How about chess? I'd make it so that every time Tony and I played other people, our queens could move any way she wanted."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could design the perfect play space for yourself, what would it have in it? Where would it be?",
			"answer": "In my space, I would have a piano and a guitar and music books.  I'd also have a karaoke system, an ipad mini, and an iPod 4.  I'd have big blow up balloons of my siblings.  I'd also have a big disco ball that you could turn on and off with a light switch. And there would be special light switches marked yellow, orange, red, green, and purple to make the room change colors."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the strangest sound you can make? What do you think it sounds the most like in nature?",
			"answer": "*makes high pitched noise* *makes weird clicking noise* I think it sounds most like a dolphin. I was going to say cicada, but it doesn't sound like that."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What part about being a kid do you think you will miss the most when you grow up? Why? What do you think I/we (the adults) miss the most? Why did you choose that?",
			"answer": "That I didn't have to pay bills and my parents took care of me. Because I don't want to use money to pay bill.  I want to buy leisurely items.  I'd way rather spend it on an expensive bedspread.  And not everyone will be as splendid as my parents. You and Daddy miss not having to pay bills, but I know you and Daddy like your jobs. I think if you got the opportunity, you'd go on a missions trip to teach kids piano for free."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your favorite word right now? What do you like about it? When have you used it recently?",
			"answer": "MERF!? Because merf is an awesome word.  And it's my word.  And Maggie's word.  Case closed."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could swap places with anyone in the world for just a day, who would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "An unmarried princess.  I don't really know of any that are unmarried, cause I only know of one princess.  I want to see how princesses live and see if their lives are as hard as everyone says they are."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you think would be the best thing about being a dog or cat? Why? What would be the worst thing? Why?",
			"answer": "The best thing about being a dog would be sprinting for a long time without gettting tired and I'd get played with a lot.  The worst would be having black and white eyesight and having to eat disgusting dog food.  The worst part of being a cat would be barfing hairballs a lot."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could double the time you spend on just one subject in school, what would you choose? Why? What subject would you give up in order to do that? Why?",
			"answer": "Reading, because I really like reading.  It feeds my brain information I didn't know before. I'd would probably give up science or social studies."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the most awesome thing you've ever seen? What made it so awesome?",
			"answer": "Seeing someone stand on a pole while doing tricks with a soccer ball. It was amazing that he was able to stand on one foot and balance while he was moving the ball around his leg and dribbling it on top of his head.  It was amazing."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is one thing that you think you will definitely be great at when you are an adult? Why?",
			"answer": "READING! Because I'm already great at it and it would be kind of hard to learn how to read really, really well and then forget how to read."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2016-06-12",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite activity?",
			"answer": "Reading."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Where is your least favorite place to go that you sometimes have to go to?",
			"answer": "Uh.....I don't know."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could change one law, what would it be?",
			"answer": "I would revoke the legalization of abortion"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What are the three best things about being you?",
			"answer": "I'm beautiful, I'm happy, and I'm the oldest."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your dad?",
			"answer": "Best: I like that he doesn't get angry quickly; Least: uh...maybe when he's like playing a video game and I try to talk to him and he won't answer for a really long time."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your mom?",
			"answer": "Best: that she is very good at caring for people. She is empathetic.; Least: (she didn't want to answer this one)"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is one thing that scares you?",
			"answer": "Everyone dying."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?",
			"answer": "One time a friend gave a poster thingy that described how much I meant to her."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could time-travel, where and when would you go?",
			"answer": "I would go to ... This is a hard one ... I would probably go back to the zero-hundreds and visit the Garden of Eden. And if I couldn't go there, I'd probably go back to the medieval period in England."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Where does your dad work and what does he do there?",
			"answer": "Dad works at ... I can name all his companies up until now!!! He never told me!! He works at that job that we haven't been to yet where they work on Microsoft computers and it's probably a big, grey scary building where all the people seem dull, but they're not really dull. He works on a lot of websites and he's in the top level, so that means he's the best."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you had three wishes, what would they be?",
			"answer": "1. I'd wish for world peace, cause I'm a great person like that; 2. That everyone in The world would come out of poverty.; 3. That I had 100 more wishes."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the hardest thing about being a child?",
			"answer": "Not getting to eat candy whenever you want. And I can't drive."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could have one superpower, what would it be and why?",
			"answer": "Oooo!! I'd Have the power to read minds so I could fix any situation ever."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could be anyone in the world for a day, who would it be and why?",
			"answer": "I'd would be the POTUS so that I could tour the White House."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What makes you sad?",
			"answer": "Everybody dying"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Which five words describe you best?",
			"answer": "Bubbly, amazing, magnificent, perfect, and emoji."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could only use one word each to describe your siblings, what word would you use for each one?",
			"answer": "Tony: Awesome; Harmony: pushy, but in a positive way; Charity: Pikachu; Chase: fun"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "An author or a programmer"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the earliest memory that you have?",
			"answer": "In our old house I was in our kitchen and me and Tony were sitting at the table and you had made him waffles or pancakes and I was trying to eat them."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "It would be, like, don't give two people a job together without giving them specific jobs to do separately, because then one person ends up doing way more work than the other."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the hardest thing about being a teen?", "answer": "Probably all of the homework... or work in general, I guess."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What does Heaven look like?", "answer": "It's like everything is... the ground is super white.  And the horizon is super white and there's gold on top of the towers.  and there's like this really clear river, and if you step on top of it, it'll break."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What's the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?", "answer": "When my friend Naomi tried to reimburse me for a notebook I bought for her."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "Which five words describe you best?", "answer": "Intellectual.  Literary.  Outspoken.  Opinionated.  and.... uh.... let's do... Revived."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What are the five best things about being you?", "answer": "I'm good at reading.  And I have a good family, and I have a pretty empty schedule, so I can be spontaneous.  And I have a good foundation for, like, education.  And I can learn things quickly."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "Can you name one thing that scares you?", "answer": "Personal financial crisis."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?", "answer": "An editor for works of literature.  Literary editor?  Is that what they're called?  I need to look that up."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the most amazing thing you've ever heard?", "answer": "The song \"Amazing Grace\""},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What will be the hardest part about being a grown-up?", "answer": "Worrying constantly about the way I'm influencing my children's decisions and if I am doing parenting correctly.  Like it feels like i would be making it up as I went along."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could make one new law, what would it be?", "answer": "I would make abortion illegal."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What is your favorite family tradition?", "answer": "We don't really have that many family traditions, but my favorite tradition is going over to Mimi's house on Christmas Eve.  That's always fun."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is the best thing about mom?  Worst thing about mom?  Best thing about dad?  Worst thing about dad?", "answer": "Best thing about mom is she is very invested in her kids' lives.  The worst thing about mom is when she makes that face with all of her teeth showing and her eyes really big.  The best thing about dad is that he welcomes different opinions and does his best to answer questions.  And the worst thing about Dad is that he loves work too much."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the funniest thing you've ever seen?", "answer": "The Miraculous Christmas Special.  It's funny 'cuz it's so bad."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could be any cartoon character for a day, who would it be and why?", "answer": "I'd be Timmy Turner from Fairly Odd Parents 'cuz I could pretty much get whatever I want."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What would you do with $100?", "answer": "I'd buy a week-long supply of Chocolate Milk.  (Dad: the most expensive chocolate milk in the world, I guess.)  No, $100 would only buy me like 55 chocolate milks at Dollar General!"}
		]
	}],
	"tony": [
	{
		"qDate": "2012-05-18",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "The first time I met Noah (church friend)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "Because you have toys, and you can play video games, and candy."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "That I was born."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "Give us lunch."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "T-Rex, and it's because they're cool, and they're strong, and they're tall."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "Play with my friends."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "A book that Angel and me read at night – Nursery rhymes.  We read it in different languages, so it's more funny."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Play on the iPad, because it has a whole bunch of games that I like."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Play Star Wars and Batman Avengers and stuff."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings? ",
			"answer": "Angel plays with me a lot.  Charity walks up to me a lot.  And Harmony? ... That sometimes Harmony plays with me."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "I played with my friends when they asked me."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "I would be in High School, and I will do homework and I'm gonna have to have lunch money."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Um... go at the pool."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "I would say $30, and I would buy that toy spider web gun."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "When their hair looks nice; when they have nice clothes on."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
			"answer": "We could go to a special place to eat, and we could go to Lego Land together."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
			"answer": "Looking at dirty dishes."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
			"answer": "I would buy food, video games, and toys, and a house... like a skyscraper if I could."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "A police officer, because they get a lot of money, and they save people, and they take villains to jail, and they have a light car... ya know, those lights... and they have a little thing that tells how fast cars are going, and they have computers."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
			"answer": "Umm... 10 feet tall? ... Oh I’m guessing daddy’s 12 feet tall"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
			"answer": "10 feet tall"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
			"answer": "You work on the internet."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
			"answer": "Um... um like if someone’s a superstar then people can put it on a commercial and get things on internets and put it on Netflix."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
			"answer": "Because he wanted to because he knew that I’d be good for you."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Why do you think the sky is blue?",
			"answer": "Because Jesus is creative and he wanted to paint the sky blue."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2014-08-17",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could spend your time doing only one activity, what would that activity be? Why?",
			"answer": "Playing video games because it entertains me."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could learn how to do something new next week, what would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "Kinda would want to learn a sport... \"What sport?\" Oh...whatever sport."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could do something to cheer up a group of kids less fortunate than you, what would you do? Why?",
			"answer": "I would give the orphanage money and um... hand out presents for them."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could pick something in your bedroom that would last forever, what would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "Legos.  No reason."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could send an e-mail or text message to anyone in the world knowing that they would in fact open it and read it, to whom would you send it? What would you say? Why?",
			"answer": "To my Dad.  It would say: \"Dad, I love you.\"  Why? Because I love you."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could have a super power, what would you choose to have? Why? What super-hero name would you choose?",
			"answer": "Invincibility. Because I couldn't get hurt and I would never die. I would be named Invincible Man."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could have any animal in the world and shrink it down to a mouse-sized pet, what animal would you choose? Why? What name would you give it? Why?",
			"answer": "I would choose a dinosaur, because if it was small it would be easy to take out its teeth."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Where do you think would be the most exciting place in the United States to live? To visit? How about in the world?",
			"answer": "Canada.  Because it has Disneyworld there.  Doesn't it have Disneyworld there?  \"To visit?\"  Florida.  \"In the whole world?\" Kansas.  Because my friends are here."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Can you think of three things we could do to make meals together more interesting and fun for everyone in the family?",
			"answer": "Able to let the kids make it theirself but with help if they wanted."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the silliest thing you've ever done? What would you like to do to top it? Why?",
			"answer": "When I was two, I went up to my mom and said a bunch of random stuff in gibberish, and she didn't know what I was saying, and she answered \"Really?\" and I said \"Uh huh!\" and I got all happy and stuff.  \"Top It?\"  I don't know."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your favorite sport or game? If you could change one rule, what would you change? Why?",
			"answer": "Basketball and if it would be a game, it would also be Minecraft.  I wouldn't say Roblox cuz it's a website.  If I could change one rule about basketball, I would say to make the rule that the youngest person named Tony on any team could make the team win whenever he wants."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could design the perfect play space for yourself, what would it have in it? Where would it be?",
			"answer": "It would have Xbox, Playstation 4, Nintendo 64, Wii U, Five controllers with motion plusses built inside, 5 nunchucks, TV, a sofa, and two lamps, and NES, and 4 wavebirds (controllers), and a fan, and a bed.  Oh wait! And a carpet.  Where would it be?  On the right side of my house."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the strangest sound you can make? What do you think it sounds the most like in nature?",
			"answer": "Uh... that's hard because you'd just put a bunch of words to describe it. (makes a choking/swallowing/grunting sound)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What part about being a kid do you think you will miss the most when you grow up? Why? What do you think I/we (the adults) miss the most? Why did you choose that?",
			"answer": "That I didn't have to work every day.  What do you think we miss the most? The first thing that popped up into my head is that we don't get to see our mom and dad so much.  I think it's something else though."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your favorite word right now? What do you like about it? When have you used it recently?",
			"answer": "Angel's would be \"Merf\" I know that.  Okay \"Cool.\"  That's what it is."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could swap places with anyone in the world for just a day, who would you choose? Why?",
			"answer": "I would want it to be someone close to my age I know that... Um... It would be Will (next door neighbor) just because I would understand his life more."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you think would be the best thing about being a dog or cat? Why? What would be the worst thing? Why?",
			"answer": "It would definitely be a dog... it's that you would be able to do a lot of... no... not that... just that you would have more energy and stuff so that you could run around faster and longer.  And you could do a lot of stuff that people couldn't do.  The worst thing?  Is that your owners feed you horrible tasting food."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could double the time you spend on just one subject in school, what would you choose? Why? What subject would you give up in order to do that? Why?",
			"answer": "Science. Because Science is easy because I only have to read two pages a day and the words are kinda big.  Subject to give up?  Math!  Because math takes a long ti... no wait.  I wouldn't give up math because math is important.  I would give up history because history mostly has myths, and I don't need to learn them."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the most awesome thing you've ever seen? What made it so awesome?",
			"answer": "A video of a motorcycle and a truck almost crashing but having like... well, I'm not sure if this is true, but it just might be true... and then an angel came to teleport him away."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is one thing that you think you will definitely be great at when you are an adult? Why?",
			"answer": "Programming because I am getting taught programming now, so I will know a lot when I am a adult."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2016-06-12",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite activity?",
			"answer": "Playing video games, table tennis, and um... what was it called?... oh yeah, Soccer!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Where is your least favorite place to go that you sometimes have to go to?",
			"answer": "I guess... the bank, but I don't really go there that often."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could change one law, what would it be?",
			"answer": "I would change the law about the right to abortion.  I'd want abortion to be illegal."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What are the three best things about being you?",
			"answer": "A good house; not many killed people in my family (like I have a big family and stuff); and I have Christian parents."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your dad?",
			"answer": "It's kinda hard like with best because there's a lot of things, and I don't really have like a least.  I need like some options to pick from or something."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your mom?",
			"answer": "I don't know!  I don't really know anything; it's the same thing with dad."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is one thing that scares you?",
			"answer": "Um... can I say something that used to scare me?  Okay.  Well when I was younger I used to be scared that like when I died, I would have a new body and stuff (like in the Bible it says that God would renew my body) and that I wouldn't be me when I'm in Heaven (because it would be a renewed spirit).  Now I'm not scared of that, but I used to be a little afraid of that."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?",
			"answer": "Kinda hard to think because like I don't really feel like there's been any like big thing, but I guess the nicest thing a friend has done for me was they got me some game (but I don't really remember what it was)"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could time-travel, where and when would you go?",
			"answer": "I would go back to when I was like 6 and 8 or so at the house and try to help myself act better to mom because back then I was not so nice to mom."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Where does your dad work and what does he do there?",
			"answer": "I don't know where you work because you left Parnell.  I feel like I was told the name but I forgot what it was called.  But you program and make apps and random stuff like that."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you had three wishes, what would they be?",
			"answer": "I would want to, I guess, be given wisdom?  Because... that sounds like a good one.  And I would want to in the future be like a missionary or pastor or something secured so that I would actually be changing the world when I grow up.  And I would want, for the last wish?  The one part of me says that I would want to not die and go to Heaven like later in life so that I wouldn't have a painful death.  But the other side of me says that I would want other countries to try to... like for America to become a Republican... like have a Republican President and have other countries open up their eyes to America and try to manipulate it (NOTE: I think he meant \"emulate it\") so that we wouldn't have so many martyrs who kill other people because of their faith and stuff."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the hardest thing about being a child?",
			"answer": "Well, there's not really many hard things, so I guess the hardest thing would be that there's some things that I'm not able to do that people older than me are able to do... but I guess it's not really that hard, but it's just the hardest thing.  But of course there's a lot of things that I don't WANT to do, but there's other things that I kinda wish I could do like last year at Schlitterbahn I wanted to go on the Verrukt waterslide, but I was too short so I didn't get to go on it but Grandpa and Andrew got to go on it.  But actually there's pretty much no hard things about being a kid.  But actually I would say the hardest thing about being a kid is chores.  I'm not saying adults don't work as hard as kids do; I'm just saying there's not really any hard things about being a kid."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could have one superpower, what would it be and why?",
			"answer": "So just superpower or is the superpower more like a wish like anything could be it?  Superpower?  Okay, then I would say I would want the power of not being able to feel pain... like I'd still have nerves and would be able to walk but if it's a feeling I wouldn't want, that I wouldn't feel it.  So I wouldn't have a painful death and if I ever went into the army, I would be able to keep fighting and stuff and not scream my head off if I was shot."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could be anyone in the world for a day, who would it be and why?",
			"answer": "So anybody that's living today?  Okay um... I feel like I have a really easy life; I don't feel like I could make it better.  I guess I would want to be a sibling or something.  If it's summer, I'd want to be maybe Andrew or my siblings to kind of feel what it's like to be them and stuff... cause I don't really feel like anybody's getting it better than me or anything."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What makes you sad?",
			"answer": "Getting yelled at when I don't feel like I'm doing things wrong and obviously when people die.  When I know that it's somebody in my family or something that dies."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Which five words describe you best?",
			"answer": "Random, Weird, Cool, Smart, Christian"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could only use one word each to describe your siblings, what word would you use for each one?",
			"answer": "Angel: With-the-books, Harmony: Unique, Charity: Energetic, Chase: Crazy"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "I want to be a pastor or a missionary.  If pastor was a side job, then I'd want to be a coder because coding pays well "
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the earliest memory that you have?",
			"answer": "Do dreams count?  Okay.  Well it was my first nightmare when I was five.  Like my family ran out of the garage door into the house and a ghost broke down the door and the bricks fell.  And then my family disappeared (I called for mom and she wasn't there) and the ghost was following me and I ran upstairs and the ghost was following me and I went down the stairs and he ran after me and I went to the front door and was trying to unlock the door but I didn't know how to unlock the door back then and the ghost was coming up next to me and then my dream ended.  That, I'm pretty sure, was my earliest memory."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "That I need my allowance for this Saturday, I guess, because I don't really feel like there's any advice I want to give you.  So I guess just to give me the allowance this Saturday because we haven't gotten the allowance for a long time actually."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the hardest thing about being a kid?", "answer": "Umm... homework and chores."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What does Heaven look like?", "answer": "Well... what I've read and heard it's golden and has like completely clear water.  Just golden and very clean.  And perfect."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?", "answer": "One thing I remember is like getting me a Nerf gun for my birthday a long time ago."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "Which five words describe you best?", "answer": "Gamer.  What's the word that describes like \"finishes what you start\"?  Determined!... Happy.  Determined.  Gamer.  Lucky.  and ... Friendly."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What are the five best things about being you?", "answer": "Well I'm in a really big family.  And I'm in America.  And I have really good siblings and parents.  And I guess my family doesn't have many money issues or whatever.  And that I have friends next door."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "Can you name one thing that scares you?", "answer": "I guess the future?"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?", "answer": "I'd like to be like a programmer or something.  Cuz it pays well and it's kind of fun to see the outcome."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the most amazing thing you've ever heard?", "answer": "That there is a life after this life."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What will be the hardest part about being a grown-up?", "answer": "I feel like it'll be probably like... like all the financial stuff after marriage."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could make one new law, what would it be?", "answer": "That you're not allowed to kill babies even if they're in a mother's body."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What is your favorite family tradition?", "answer": "We don't really have any traditions so I'd say the Moritz Happy Birthday song.  Oh wait!  I'd actually said it's the getting a super cool birthday present from Mimi and Grandpa when you turn 10 years old."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is the best thing about mom?  Worst thing about mom?  Best thing about dad?  Worst thing about dad?", "answer": "Best thing about mom is that she helps us a ton like even if we're stubborn and rude and stuff that she still helps us.  Like when I was like 8 years old, I was not being responsible at all and didn't get my homework done until like the last minute, but mom would still help me through all that.  And the worst thing?  Maybe that she has a shorter fuse when she doesn't get much sleep so she'll get mad at me for something that is not a big deal.  For you, dad, I'd say that you make all the money and stuff so that we can have a nice house and tasty food and stuff.  And the worst?  Umm... hmm... I can't really think of anything.  Well, I guess one thing is... it's not exactly the worst part... it's just like... it would be nice if you were home more, but you're not home as much cuz you work.  So i don't like that you're not home more, but because of what your not being home as much does, i guess I do like it kinda... indirectly."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the funniest thing you've ever seen?", "answer": "Jim Gaffigan \"Four kids\" part of his Mr. Universe comedy special."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "If you could be any cartoon character for a day, who would it be and why?", "answer": "Does it have to be a cartoon character from a movie or a TV show?  (Dad: what other cartoon characters are there?)  I'd be a cartoon character from Fortnite because that would be fun to play that and if you're a cartoon character on Fortnite, then you don't die.  There's like this little drone that comes and it like pixelates you and brings you back into the lobby."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What would you do with $100?", "answer": "With $100?  I uh... I would donate it.  If I was just GIVEN $100, then I would donate it.  But if I EARNED it, then i would donate $10, and then would buy gifts or something, and then the rest I would just save for later.  So tithe, gift it, and save it for later."}
		]
	}],
	"harmony": [
	{
		"qDate": "2012-05-18",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "My apple (that she's currently eating)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "Angel and Tony and Charity and Mommy and Daddy."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "Sad for my purple pony."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "When I give you a present, it would be a pair of shoes for Daddy and a diamond ring for Mommy."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "Elephant! (makes elephant noise)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "Play on my purple computer and my toys."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "Birds eat me a lot and they poop a lot!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Purple coffee.  It's hot so I can drink it."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Play games. Like toss on the bed!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings? ",
			"answer": "Angel: a purple computer; Tony: flowers; Charity: getting lots of gummies in her mouth."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "I gave them some treats ... like that."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "Go to a church."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Bubbles!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "I would want $5 to buy a bunny."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "Getting married to a purple princess... like a prince."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
			"answer": "A spit fight... and Rock Band!!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
			"answer": "A yucky apple is yucky."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
			"answer": "With sprinkles."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
			"answer": "Uh, big."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
			"answer": "Big!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
			"answer": "Uh, work... go to your office."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "How does a tomato grow?",
			"answer": "Big beanstalk."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think Yo Gabba Gabba do when they're not on TV?",
			"answer": "Like this! (starts dancing)"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
			"answer": "Water give me, put me in my family."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
			"answer": "Uh... how about buy a bunny?  (\"Anything else?\") Nope."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "Uh... a cow.... Is that a animal? (\"Yes.\") Uh, then I want to be a elephant."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2014-08-17",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "Playing with Ava.  We don't see each other enough"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "I'd rather be a princess instead"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "A dress"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "That's a hard one..."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "A unicorn. I mean a pony.  I would be a girl pony cuz they're so pretty. And I would name it jewels and put bows on her."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "Play around. Play with my next door neighbor."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "There's never a time when I joked a bit. Yeah! We're driving to college! Ok! We're driving to college. (inside joke, kinda)"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Be a star, because everynody will notice me and will cheer for me cuz I'm SUCH a star. And I wouldl make a cereal called \"Harmony's H's\".  And it would have marshmallows and the H's would have protein in them!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Play \"Just Dance\" with them"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
			"answer": "Angel: Playing with her..., Tony: Playing with him..., Charity: Playing with her..., Chase: Playing with him..., "
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "Be nice to them. That would be easy. Oh, wait! Make a necklace for them."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "Uh, playing games. That was easy. Going to a Chick-fil-A opening."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Go to the pool! Oh, and make it Schlitterbahn."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "$100. Buy stuff.  All the the toys in the world!...the girl toys. And I wish I had a fairy that could grant me one wish and it would be 1000 wishes! No, wait. Infinity wishes."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "Make-up"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
			"answer": "Go to kids' museum and Aquarium"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
			"answer": "Oh let's see... a turtle? Those are SUPER GROSS! YUK!"
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2016-06-12",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite activity?",
			"answer": "Um...playing with Brooklyn"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Where is your least favorite place to go that you sometimes have to go to?",
			"answer": "Um...let's see... I would say Walmart, but sometimes I like it. It just depends. Actually, it would be little park."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could change one law, what would it be?",
			"answer": "That Barak Obama should not be president."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What are the three best things about being you?",
			"answer": "I have a really great family, and I have lots of toys, and I have the best friends."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your dad?",
			"answer": "Best: Daddy snuggles with me!; Least: That he works in the morning"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your mom?",
			"answer": "Best: I like that Mommy takes care of me; Least: that she yells at us."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is one thing that scares you?",
			"answer": "Poisonous spiders"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?",
			"answer": "I like that Sarah shares her toys"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could time-travel, where and when would you go?",
			"answer": "I would probably go when dragons were around or dinosaurs, cause I would get to see them. Actually, no, I would go to Jesus time!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Where does your dad work and what does he do there?",
			"answer": "He works at ... I don't know! He never told me! Um...I have no idea."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you had three wishes, what would they be?",
			"answer": "That Barak Obama wasn't president, and Ted Cruz was gonna be president,  and I could turn myself into things."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the hardest thing about being a child?",
			"answer": "That I have to do chores."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could have one superpower, what would it be and why?",
			"answer": "It would be invisibility! Cause then I could just turn invisible and punch the bad guys in the face!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could be anyone in the world for a day, who would it be and why?",
			"answer": "I would be Natalie cause she has the most toys and she's awesome."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What makes you sad?",
			"answer": "That I don't get to cuddle with Daddy anymore cause he leaves too early."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Which five words describe you best?",
			"answer": "Agent Harmo, Harms, crazy, and weird. (mom: that's only four) um....I would say five. Because I have five siblings."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could only use one word each to describe your siblings, what word would you use for each one?",
			"answer": "Angel: Reader; Tony: umm...(thinks for a long time)... Cool man; Charity: player; Chase: player 2"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "I want to be a teacher, actually no a baker. And a ninja."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the earliest memory that you have?",
			"answer": "When me and Sarah made the presents."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "To stay cool."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the hardest thing about being a kid?", "answer": "Are there options? (Mom: Nope. You just answer.) Probably not getting as many privileges."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What does Heaven look like?", "answer": "There are going to be gold streets, I think, and streams and on a cloud, like a BIG, BIG cloud that never ends so no one gets hurt.  And no thorns.  And no bugs, except for bees.  Bees are good.  And I think one house that everyone will stay in."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?", "answer": "Helped me with my chores."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "Which five words describe you best?", "answer": "Creative. Unusual. Weird. Fun. Is that four or five? (Me: four) Music."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What are the five best things about being you?", "answer": "That I live in a nice home that I never have to be afraid of losing.  Great parents.  Great friends.  That I live close to most of my friends. And my grandparents and all my other relatives.  I can have fun with them."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "Can you name one thing that scares you?", "answer": "Wasps."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?", "answer": "A violinist."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the most amazing thing you've ever heard?", "answer": "A violin. Cause it's so majestic."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What will be the hardest part about being a grown-up?", "answer": "Uh, having to pay for everything."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could make one new law, what would it be?", "answer": "To make abortion illegal again."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is your favorite family tradition?", "answer": "(whispers to self: I dunno, we don't really have any traditions...) Probably getting together each holiday."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is the best thing about mom?  Worst thing about mom?  Best thing about dad?  Worst thing about dad?", "answer": "The worst thing is that you don't let us have any electronics and the best thing is all the game consoles and board games that we have.  Best thing about mom is that she can handle so many children.  And the worst thing is that she gets mad at me over something little since some chiropractic thing.  She told me it's because a thing in her neck is getting pinched.  Best thing about Dad is... this is just a joke... \"Nothing.\"  Just kidding.  The best thing about Dad is that he buys so many game consoles and that we get to play on them.  No no no no!  Watching \"Full House\" with Dad.  That he watches \"Full House\" with me.  And the worst thing is that he locks his door sometimes.  And he always sings (singing) \"If mommy and daddy's door is locked, turn around and walk away!\""},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What's the funniest thing you've ever seen?", "answer": "I gotta be honest with you....the \"NAILED IT!\" Unicorn episode was HILARIOUS!"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "If you could be any cartoon character for a day, who would it be and why?", "answer": "Dulcinea from Puss in Boots because she's usually so nice, but when she's mad, she can break a finger."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What would you do with $100?", "answer": "Um...now, uh, this is before it happened, but I would donate it to DITEC because I wanted to save it, but now I think Church KC is going to buy it."}
		]
	}],
	"charity": [
	{
		"qDate": "2012-06-18",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite cereal?",
			"answer": "Cereal and Eggs."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What's your favorite show?",
			"answer": "A Gabba Gabba! (Yo Gabba Gabba!)"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "Mickey Mouse!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What's your favorite thing about being a kid?",
			"answer": "Mimi's house!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "Blow bubbles."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What's your favorite thing to do?",
			"answer": "A Charity, a Harmony, a Davey."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
			"answer": "Please."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like to play?",
			"answer": "Go ride."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "Daddy and Mommy and um um a Charity."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "Charity."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "Self."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "Animal?  I be Elmo."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "I freeze."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "Yesterday I had a binky.  I a elephant!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Go church."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Gabba Gabba!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
			"answer": "Tony here Tony (points to Tony in a picture).  (\"Harmony?\") That one!  (then points to Angel) Angel!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "Six.  (\"Six?\")  Yeah, six."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "Milk.... (Points to her bowl of cereal) This is milk."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Summer... hiding (she hides under the chair)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "Fish. (\"Fish?\") Yeah, fish."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "My teeth."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
			"answer": "Brush a hair."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
			"answer": "Daddy at work a Elmo."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
			"answer": "TV a Gabba Gabba."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you think Yo Gabba Gabba do when they're not on TV?",
			"answer": "TV!  Hahaha!"
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2014-08-17",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
			"answer": "My happiest memory is giving Daddy a card"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
			"answer": "Because I can said letters to Dad, like cards and stuff. Cause I love Daddy"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
			"answer": "Giving Dad notes"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "Give cards"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
			"answer": "I would be a giraffe in the race game because it has a lot of health"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
			"answer": "Play Pikmin"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
			"answer": "Telling jokes. I laugh so hard, water comes out my eyes"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
			"answer": "Playing the iPad. Because they make a swatch movie and God forgave our sin so we can be in heaven."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
			"answer": "Play tag"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
			"answer": "Angel: her tea parties; Tony: playing games, like Pikmin; Harmony: King of the Castle; Chase: playing run around the rosie"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
			"answer": "Play with them"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
			"answer": "Playing hide n seek"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
			"answer": "Sending celebrations and opening presents"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
			"answer": "$2000. I would use it to pay the bank"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "Playing and napping"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
			"answer": "Play puzzles, play with cars, and Harmony"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
			"answer": "Really stinky pie"
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2016-06-12",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite activity?",
			"answer": "Color pictures"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "Where is your least favorite place to go that you sometimes have to go to?",
			"answer": "The bank"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could change one law, what would it be?",
			"answer": "You have to eat cake everyday."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What are the three best things about being you?",
			"answer": "That we're really nice to friends, and we sometimes play chalk with each other, and we can have sleepovers"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your dad?",
			"answer": "Best: that he plays Kirby and the Rainbow Curse with us; Least: that he always goes to work when I want to play with him."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your mom?",
			"answer": "Best: that's it's good for her to do work.; Least: that she does do work, but I want to play with her."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is one thing that scares you?",
			"answer": "Dinosaurs."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?",
			"answer": "She gave me one of her toys and she gave me nerds on my birthday."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could time-travel, where and when would you go?",
			"answer": "I'd go to the dinosaur place where the robot dinosaurs are."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Where does your dad work and what does he do there?",
			"answer": "My dad works at his work. I don't know what it's called. Sometimes we go visit him and he does lots of work."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you had three wishes, what would they be?",
			"answer": "I wish I could go anywhere I want. And I would wish it would be my birthday everyday so I can get lots and lots of presents. And my third wish would be that I could have all the games in the world. Well, all the Pikachu games, I guess."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What is the hardest thing about being a child?",
			"answer": "That I always trip over and get booboos and it's hard to get back up."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could have one superpower, what would it be and why?",
			"answer": "I would fly because Superpowers are really cool!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could be anyone in the world for a day, who would it be and why?",
			"answer": "I would be Ariel because I like mermaids."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What makes you sad?",
			"answer": "That friends sometimes move away."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Which five words describe you best?",
			"answer": "I really like myself and it's really fun to play with each other and it's good we're humans. And I like our bed because it's fluffy."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could only use one word each to describe your siblings, what word would you use for each one?",
			"answer": "Angel: she's really good at looking pretty; Tony: really strong; Harmony: she's good at giving me rewards; Chase: he likes to play with me on Super Mario 3D world"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "A Mermaid"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the earliest memory that you have?",
			"answer": "That I have a dream of zombies every night."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "That they really like me and they love me so much."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the hardest thing about being a kid?", "answer": "Doing my math."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What does Heaven look like?", "answer": "It's all diamond."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?", "answer": "Help me with spelling."},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "Which five words describe you best?", "answer": "Cute, clumsy, weird, silly, kind of dumb"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What are the five best things about being you?", "answer": "Having a great family; um...I have a good room; um...I like cleaning the house, cause I like doing that; um...uh...one more thing...wait are you actually typing that?? I get good food."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "Can you name one thing that scares you?", "answer": "When Tony pops up I cry."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?", "answer": "A good mom."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the most amazing thing you've ever heard?", "answer": "I dunno. Um...Watermelons are delicious!!"},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What will be the hardest part about being a grown-up?", "answer": "Having kids."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "If you could make one new law, what would it be?", "answer": "It would be you don't have to work for money."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What is your favorite family tradition?", "answer": "Christmas?"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is the best thing about mom?  Worst thing about mom?  Best thing about dad?  Worst thing about dad?", "answer": "Worst things is if I do something really bad I get grounded and the best things is that they love me very much.  Best thing about mom is she watches shows with me?  The worst thing about mom iiisss... she gives me spankins?  The best thing about dad is that he plays \"Look a little closer with me\"?  And the worst thing about dad is that if I do something really really bad I get grounded.  (Dad: when have I grounded you?)  You never.  But that's the worst thing!"},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What's the funniest thing you've ever seen?", "answer": "PANCAKES!!"},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could be any cartoon character for a day, who would it be and why?", "answer": "Rena Rouge because she's the best superhero."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What would you do with $100?", "answer": "Spend it on toys, food, and video games."}
		]
	}],
	"chase": [
	{
		"qDate": "2012-07-20",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Hi little guy!",
			"answer": "Waa! Waa! Waaaaaaa!!!"
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2014-08-17",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
			"answer": "A ball!"
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2016-06-12",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is your favorite activity?",
			"answer": "Play games"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Where is your least favorite place to go that you sometimes have to go to?",
			"answer": "It is church cause you're taking for long at church"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could change one law, what would it be?",
			"answer": "It is toys"
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What are the three best things about being you?",
			"answer": "Play some toys, and I love playing the cat game (a.k.a. Super Mario 3D World)."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your dad?",
			"answer": "Best: I play games with him; Least: he plays Uncharted."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What do you like best--and what do you like least--about your mom?",
			"answer": "Best: Snuggle with her; Least: she plays games with Charity"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is one thing that scares you?",
			"answer": "Zombies"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?",
			"answer": "Sarah was nice"
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "If you could time-travel, where and when would you go?",
			"answer": "At Fun run"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Where does your dad work and what does he do there?",
			"answer": "He works at work. He works and he's in the cow chair and the tables."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you had three wishes, what would they be?",
			"answer": "I wish I had lots of toys. I wish that I had a game that was Pokemon tournament.  I wish that I wanted a Pichu doll."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "What is the hardest thing about being a child?",
			"answer": "Playing games."
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could have one superpower, what would it be and why?",
			"answer": "SUPERMAN!! Cause Superman kills bad guys."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "If you could be anyone in the world for a day, who would it be and why?",
			"answer": "Grandpa cause I really like grandpa."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What makes you sad?",
			"answer": "Getting hurt"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "Which five words describe you best?",
			"answer": "Toys!"
		},
		{
			"rating": 2,
			"question": "If you could only use one word each to describe your siblings, what word would you use for each one?",
			"answer": "Angel: I zerbert her; Tony: I zerbert him; Harmony: I zerbert Harmony, too!; Charity: zerbert."
		},
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
			"answer": "Four."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What is the earliest memory that you have?",
			"answer": "A book."
		},
		{
			"rating": 1,
			"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
			"answer": "A zerbert. And play games with me."
		}]
	},
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the hardest thing about being a kid?", "answer": "Reading?"},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What does Heaven look like?", "answer": "Clouds."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What's the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?", "answer": "Well, Sarah gave me LOTS of cars!"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "Which five words describe you best?", "answer": "Pancake. Waffle. Cake. Cupcake. Baby."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What are the five best things about being you?", "answer": "Reading.  Finishing a book by myself.  Mom helping me read a book.  Tony helping me read a book.  Mom AND Tony helping me read a book!"},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "Can you name one thing that scares you?", "answer": "People sneaking up on me.  One time Tony scared me so hard that my stomach started to hurt."},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?", "answer": "A coder."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What's the most amazing thing you've ever heard?", "answer": "Speedrunning without Cappy going away on Mario Odyssey!"},
			{"rating": 1, "question": "What will be the hardest part about being a grown-up?", "answer": "About working."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "If you could make one new law, what would it be?", "answer": "That you only make macaroni and... what was it called again?  Pasta bratwurst!"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is your favorite family tradition?", "answer": "Family game night.  And staycation!  I LOVE staycation!  Cuz one time we did a staycation and I wanted to get Mario cereal!"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What is the best thing about mom?  Worst thing about mom?  Best thing about dad?  Worst thing about dad?", "answer": "Mom: about that she gives me hugs and kisses and she helps me read a book and we can watch movies together.  Worst thing is that she gives me spankins.  And that she sometimes gets me in trouble.  And that's it.  Dad: About that we can play parks together and i can get better on it and that you give me hugs and kisses and we can play board games together.  And that I can watch you play Celeste.  And that's it.  And the worst thing is that you give me hand pinches and that you sometimes get me in trouble.  And that's it."},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What's the funniest thing you've ever seen?", "answer": "Like on a video game or something?  That you do funny jokes on me like knock knock jokes.  It's super funny!"},
			{"rating": 2, "question": "If you could be any cartoon character for a day, who would it be and why?", "answer": "It's so hard!  Dad, dad, this is super hard.  I can't find out... the FLASH!  Is the Flash a cartoon character?"},
			{"rating": 3, "question": "What would you do with $100?", "answer": "This is really hard... tons of things are really expensive... Buy stuff at the... what's it called again?  TARGET!  Buy stuff at Target. (Dad: what would you buy there?)  Um... I would pay for really fun toys that were less money.  And I would buuuyyy... candy.  Dad, how much are cars?  (Dad: real cars?)  Yeah.  (Dad: they're about $10,000).  That's so much!  I would buy toy cars."}
		]
	}],
	"symphony": [
	{
		"qDate": "2018-07-04",
		"questions": [
		{
			"rating": 3,
			"question": "Hi sweet girl!",
			"answer": "Waa! Waa! Waaaaaaa!!!"
		}]
	}]
}
